Lillian Moller Gilbreth Papers, 1860-1999
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES VI. OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - 16 mm film recording of speech at Waseda University, Tokyo, undated (Box 15a)
  - Beret worn by Gilbreth "on visits to her children or to suburban friends," undated (Box 15a)
  - House keys with gold anagramed key ring, undated (Box 15a)
  - Framed poem, "Our Teamwork Kitchen," circa 1950s (Box 15a)
  - Miscellaneous cards, undated (Box 15a)
  - Nametag, undated (Box 15a)
  - Sewing bag with provisions, undated (Box 15a)
- BOOKS ON SHELF
  - Boorstin, Daniel J., Portraits from the Americans: The Democratic Experience, 1975
  - Copley, Frank, The Life of Frederick Taylor, copy with Frank Gilbreth's margin notes,, undated
  - Dvorak, August, Nellie L. Merrick, William L. Dealey, and Gertrude Catherine Ford, Typewriting Behavior: Psychology Applied to Teaching and Learning Typewriting, 1936
  - Gilbreth, Frank B., Jr., Ancestors of the Dozen, 1994
  - Gilbreth, Lillian, M., Psychology of Management, 1921
  - Gilbreth, Lillian, M., The Quest for the One Best Way, reprint 1990
  - Peabody, Josephine Preston, The Piper, 1910